Finding aid to the Office of the President Thomas Corwin Mendenhall Files. CA.MS.00032
Smith College Archives
- Series XVI. SPEECHES, 2.083 linear feet (5 containers)
  - Smith Assembly, APR 22, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Smith Assembly-S-pins & Alpha Awards, APR 29, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Sky-Top?-"The Care and Feeding of the Liberal Arts Curriculum", APR 1964 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Kent School Commencement-"Education: Formal & Informal", JUN 11, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Inst. of Critical Issues in Higher Education, Boston College-"The Intellectual Climate of the College Community", JUN 15, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Advanced Placement Conference, Boulder, CO, JUN 25, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Smith Assembly-Last Chapel, JUN 1964 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Smith Alumnae College, Spring 1964 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Smith Assembly-First Chapel, SEP 22, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Converse College, Spartanburg, SC-"The Perils and Pleasures of Being an Educated Woman", SEP 24, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Smith Assembly-Introducing the Dean, SEP 30, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Smith Admissions Conference, OCT 1, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Smith Assembly, OCT 14, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Smith Assembly-Smith College Medals, OCT 21, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - The Club, OCT 26, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Smith Assembly, OCT 28, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Vermont, OCT 1964 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - 90th Anniversary of Mt. Vernon Seminary, Washington, D.C., NOV 6, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Washington, D.C. Smith Club-"A Changing Curriculum...", NOV 6, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Smith Assembly-International Students Day, NOV 18, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Smith Assembly, DEC 2, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Smith Assembly, DEC 4, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Smith Assembly, DEC 9, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Ad Hoc Cttee Report-"The Care & Feeding of the Liberal Arts Curriculum", 1964 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Smith Alumnae Association, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Smith Alumnae Council, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Smith Rally Day, FEB 20, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Smith Assembly, MAR 10, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Smith Assembly, APR 7, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Smith Assembly, APR 14, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Smith Assembly, APR 21, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Smith Assembly-S-pins & Alpha Awards, APR 28, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Smith Assembly-Prize Day, MAY 5, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Kent Place School, Summit, NJ-Retirement Party, MAY 14, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - St. Margaret's School Centennial-"The Independent School and the Independent Woman", MAY 16, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Wells College Commencement-"Thought, Word & Deed", MAY 31, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Smith Assembly-Last Chapel, JUN 4, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Prospect Hill School Commencement, JUN 9, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Oxford School Commencement, JUN 9, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Smith Alumnae College, Spring 1965 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Smith Assembly-First Chapel, SEP 1965 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Smith Faculty Meeting, SEP 22, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Smith Assembly, OCT 6, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Smith Assembly, OCT 13, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Smith Assembly, OCT 20, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Beard School, Orange, NJ, 75th Anniversary-"Some Primary Purposes for Secondary Education", OCT 23, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Smith Assembly-Introducing the Dean, OCT 29, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Smith Assembly-Smith College Medals, NOV 4, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Low-Heywood School, Stamford, CT, Centennial Celebration, NOV 7, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Smith Assembly-International Students Day, NOV 10, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Amherst College Chapel, NOV 23, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Smith Assembly, DEC 1, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Smith Assembly, DEC 8, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Smith Alumnae Council, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - History, Historians, and the Liberal Arts, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - On Cleaning One's Desk, or Random Thoughts on Higher Education in 1965 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Smith Rally Day, FEB 26, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Smith Assembly, MAR 15, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Smith Assembly, APR 13, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Smith Assembly, APR 20, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Amer. Assoc. of University Women-"The Perils and Pleasures of Being an Educated Woman", APR 20, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Smith Assembly-Prize Day, APR 1966 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Smith Alumnae College, JUN 2, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Smith Assembly-Last Chapel, JUN 3, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Mac Duffie School Commencement, JUN 7, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Pierce College, Greece-"The Education of Women & Progress of the Race", JUN 17, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Smith Assembly-First Chapel, SEP 1966 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Smith Assembly-Introducing the Dean, SEP 21, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Smith Assembly-"Security", OCT 5?, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Smith Assembly, OCT 12, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Smith Assembly, OCT 19, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Smith Assembly-Smith College Medals, NOV 2, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Smith Assembly-International Students Day, NOV 9, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Smith Assembly-"Why Assemblies", NOV 16, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Smith Assembly, NOV 30, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Smith Alumnae Council, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - "Smith College: Present and Future", 1966 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - "Educating Women to Meet Today's Pressures", 1966 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - NY Smith Club-"The Care & Feeding of the Liberal Arts Curriculum", 1966 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Smith Assembly, FEB 1, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Smith Assembly, FEB 8, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Smith Assembly-Marion Wright Introduction, FEB 15, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Smith Rally Day, FEB 25, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Boston Smith Club-"Student Restlessness", APR 13, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Northampton High School-"Some Purposes for Education", APR 13, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Smith Assembly-S-pins & Alpha Awards, APR 26, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Smith Assembly-Prize Day, MAY 3, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Clark Science Center Dedication, MAY 6, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Smith Alumnae College, MAY 31, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Smith College Relief Unit Celebration, JUN 3, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Smith Commencement-Nicholas Katzenbach Introduction, JUN 4, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Beaver Country Day School Commencement-"On Being an Intellectual", JUN 9, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Clarke School Commencement, JUN 13, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Smith Assembly-Last Chapel, JUN 1967 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Smith Assembly-First Chapel, SEP 19, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Smith Assembly-Introducing the Dean, OCT 4, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Parents' Day, OCT 6, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Colby Junior College, OCT 19, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Springfield Federation of Teachers-"The Teacher: Participant or Bystander", OCT 20, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Smith Assembly-Smith College Medals, OCT 25, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Smith Assembly, DEC 7, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Smith Alumnae Council, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Boston Smith Club (?), JAN 10, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - San Francisco Smith Club, JAN 1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Smith Assembly-"Some Comments about Smith as a Community", FEB 7, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Smith Rally Day, FEB 24, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Meeting, MAR 13, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - New York Smith Club (?), APR 29, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Smith Assembly-Prize Day, MAY 1, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Last Burnham School Commencement, MAY 26, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Smith Assembly-Last Chapel, MAY 31, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Smith School for Social Work 50th Anniversary, JUL 27, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Smith Assembly-First Chapel, SEP 17, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Smith Assembly-Introducing the Dean, SEP 30, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - "Minnesota Kick-Off", OCT 9, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Smith Assembly-Smith College Medals, OCT 23, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Smith Alumnae Council, OCT 24, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Central Pennsylvania Smith Club, OCT 31, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - St. Mary's Episcopal School, Memphis, TN, Centennial, NOV 1, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "Chicago's Leadership", NOV 21, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Washington Smith Club (?), JAN 29, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Smith Rally Day, FEB 22, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Kansas City Smith Club (?), MAR 7, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Smith Assembly-Student Unrest, APR 28, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Smith Assembly-Last Chapel, JUN 1969 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Smith Alumnae College, Spring 1969 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Smith Assembly-First Chapel, SEP 17, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Smith Assembly-Smith College Medals, OCT 22, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Smith Alumnae College Meeting, OCT 23, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Association of American Colleges-"Admissions Policy: Implications & Consequences", JAN 1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Smith Rally Day, FEB 20, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Smith Assembly, MAY 4, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Smith Assembly-Last Chapel, MAY 29, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Smith Alumnae College, Spring 1970 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Smith Assembly-First Chapel, SEP 15, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Library Dedication, Loomis & Chaffee Schools, Windsor, CT, OCT 18, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Smith Assembly-Smith College Medals, OCT 21, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Smith Assembly, FEB 8, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Smith Rally Day, FEB 19, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Hampshire Smith Club Meeting, APR 14, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Meeting, APR 25, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Medical College of Pennsylvania Commencement-"South for the Winter", MAY 26, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Smith Assembly-Last Chapel, MAY 28, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Smith Alumnae College, Spring 1971 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Smith Assembly-First Chapel, SEP 12, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Smith Assembly-Smith College Medals, OCT 20, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Smith Assembly, Fall 1971 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Cum Laude Society of Exeter, NH, FEB 10, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Smith Rally Day, FEB 23, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Smith Assembly-Last Chapel, MAY 26, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Smith Alumnae College, MAY 1972 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Smith Assembly-First Chapel, SEP 10, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - "Why Smith?", 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Smith Rally Day, FEB 1973 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - "Some Reflections on an Alleged Male Chauvinist", APR 1973 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Smith Alumnae College, MAY 1973 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Smith Assembly-Last Chapel, MAY 10, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Milton Academy Commencement, JUN 8, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Smith Assembly-First Chapel, SEP 9, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Miss Hall's School 75th Anniversary, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Smith Rally Day, FEB 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Smith Assembly-Last Chapel, MAY 31, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Smith Alumnae College, MAY 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Smith Assembly-First Chapel/Convocation, SEP 8, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Smith Katharine Asher Engel Lecture-"Chance and Change...", 1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Washington Smith Club Meeting, JAN 30, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Smith Rally Day, FEB 26, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Smith Centennial History Symposium, APR 1975 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Smith Hills Chapel Service-"A Charge to the Congregation", MAY 11, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Smith Assembly-Last Chapel, MAY 30, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Smith Commencement Poems, 1962-1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - "The College and the Community", undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Education and Revolution", undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - "Every Woman Her Own Historian", undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Freedom, Responsibility and Service, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - "The Future of Women's Education", undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - "Higher Education For Women: For Better or Worse", undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - "Higher Education For Women and Women Working", undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - "Leaders and Leadership on the College Campus", undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - "The Massachusetts Librarian", undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - "My Theory: Changing to Remain the Same", undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - "The Professor & His Profession: Some Thoughts on Education", undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - "The Public Posture of the Private College", undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Williston School Cum Laude-"Quality & Equality in American Education", undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - "Some Comments About Smith as a Community", undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Some Random, Amateur Thoughts on the Difference Between Amateurs and Professionals, Especially in Sports, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - "Women in Modern Society", undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Amherst College Parents Lunch, MAY 27; 19?? (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Boston Luncheon, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Miss Hall's School, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Northampton School for Girls, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Smith Academy, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Smith Alumnae Club?, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Smith School for Social Work, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Fragments, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Notes for Quotes-Categorized, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Notes for Quotes, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Series XVII. STUDENTS, 1.667 linear feet (4 containers)
  The records in this series document the relationship of the Smith student body with the faculty and administration of the college. The bulk of the series relates to the student unrest which in so many ways defined the era of Mendenhall's presidency. There are also records of more traditional student organizations and activities, such as student government, publications and extracurriculars. Information about students can also be found in the records of Committees & Boards with student representation, as well as in the records of specific student residences in the Buildings & Grounds series.
  - General, 1960-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alcohol, 1961-1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alcohol, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alcohol, 1969-1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Automobile Regulations, 1961-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Christian Scientists
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Health Services- Christian Science
  - Drugs, 1966-1971; undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Individuals, Correspondence with, 1959-1975; undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Individuals-Nixon, Julie, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - International Students, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    see also Series IX. Committees & Boards- Foreign Students, Committee on
  - International Students, 1964-1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minority Students
    See Series XVII. Students-Organizations-Black Students' Alliance -and- Series IX. Committees & Boards-Student Affairs, Committee on- Committee of Six -and- Series V. Administrative Offices-Admissions -and- Series XIV. Intercollegiate Associations-Five Colleges-Students-Minorities -and- Series XIV. Intercollegiate Associations-Five Colleges-Acad. Progs-Afro-American Studies
  - Organizations, -AIESEC 1967-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Black Students' Alliance, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Black Students' Alliance, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Black Students' Alliance, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Black Students' Alliance-1970 Demands (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Black Students' Alliance-Vehicle, 1970-1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1959-1964 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Debating Club, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Honor Board, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - International Relations Club, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Judicial Board, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - NAACP, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - National Student Association, 1959-1967 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Recreational Council, 1962-1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Service Organizations of Smith, 1967-1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Service Organizations of Smith-1968-1971 Report (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Service Organizations of Smith-M. L. King, Jr. Fund, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Student Government Association, 1959-1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee:
      See Series X. Engagements-March 1965, for a letter from John Lewis.
  - Parents, Correspondence with, 1960-1975; undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Parietal Regulations, 1964-1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    see also Series IX. Ctees & Bds-Student Affairs, Cttee on
  - Parietal Regulations-Alumnae Correspondence, 1964-1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Parietal Regulations-Residency Requirement, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Publications-Grecourt Review, 1959-1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Publications-Hamper [Yearbook], 1964 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Publications-Sophian, 1960-1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Sexuality, 1962-1968; 1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Student Centers-CPA Student Lounge, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Davis Student Center, 1959-1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Lilly Pad/Cellar Door, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Mwangi Cultural Center, 1969-1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Unrest-General, 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    see also Series IX. Committees & Boards-Social Responsibility, Committee on -and- Series IX. Committees & Boards-Student Affairs, Committee on -and- Series XIII. Graduate Work-School for Social Work-Student Unrest
    - General, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - General-News Clippings & Articles, 1966; 1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - General-Correspondence w/Legislators, 1961-1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - General-Fasting, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - General-People's Lobby, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Antiwar, 1962-1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - College Policies, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Spring of 1970-News Clippings & Articles, MAY-OCT 1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Five Colleges, MAY 1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Administrative Response, MAY-JUL 1970 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Faculty Response, MAY-JUL 1970 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Graduation, MAY-JUN 1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Student Response, MAY-AUG 1970 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Student Response-Smith Strike Committee, MAY 1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence from Alumnae, MAY 11-19, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence from Alumnae, MAY 20-24, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence from Alumnae, MAY 25-JUN; 1970 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence from Alumnae, JUL-AUG 1970; undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence from Parents, MAY-JUN; 1970 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous, MAY 1970 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Series XVIII. PHOTOGRAPHS, 1.25 linear feet (3 containers)
  The photographs in this series document many of the events and activities described in the printed material. Additional photographs may be found in the Hampshire College Records (70.Org.H.C.), the Honorary Degree records (12.HD), and in the class records under Ivy Day and Commencement. There are also slides and film footage of the inauguration in the audio-visual collection (see list at the end of the Photographs folder listing).
  - Portraits, 1959-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Portraits, 1968-1975; undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Portraits-Official Portrait Painted by Peter Egel, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Family, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Family-Cornelia Mendenhall, 1959-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rowing, 1968; 1975; undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alumnae, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alumnae, 1971-1978; undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees, 1962; 1967; 1970; undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - College & Universities, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Events-Commencement, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Commencement, 1970-1975; undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Inauguration-Crowd Shots, Oct. 15, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Individuals, Oct. 15, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Procession, Oct. 15, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - T. C. Mendenhall, Oct. 15, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Yale University Board, Oct. 15, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Guest Speakers, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Ivy Day, 1960-1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Ivy Day, 1975; undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Rally Day, 1960-1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1959-1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1975; undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Faculty/Staff, 1959-1982; undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Intercollegiate Associations-Five Colleges, 1961-1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Students, 1960-1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Students, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1960-1967 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- SLIDES OF THE INAUGURATION IN THE A/V COLLECTION
  - Autumn tree, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Autumn road, hills, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Autumn wall, back lighting, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Vegetable stand, Sunderland, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Roadside stand, pumpkin figure, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Pumpkins on fence, near Greenfield, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Pumpkins, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Paradise, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - The President's house, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Tree by boathouse, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Faculty Club, in construction, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Dewey House without Wallace, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Edwards Church, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - 3 other views of the church: 13A, 13B, 13C, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - The Chapel (missing), OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Alumnae House with flag, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Inauguration Committee, across table, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Official car, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Registration of alumnae, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Registration of delegates, also 19A, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Boxes of gowns, men delegates, also 20A, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Boxes for women delegates, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Delegates, Anslow, escort, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Concert, quartet, Mozart, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Sexter, Etler, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Duke and Stahl (missing), OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Art, Erving, by Copley, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Modern section, Pollock, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - A. Marie Laurencia, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Andre Derain "Turn of the Road" on Loan from B. Wintersteen, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Library exhibit, art and music, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Library exhibit, Presidential publications, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Bicycles and signs, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Playing field, from distance (missing), OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Red bridge, Dam beyond, Spire (missing), OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - 3 archers at target, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Hockey, goalie, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Dam over flowers, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Ziskind luncheon (missing), OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Ziskind, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Entrance to Quad, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Terrace, Scales and King (missing), OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Laura Hodgkinson, President Gettell, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - President Gettell (missing), OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Delegates, waiting in line, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Lines on terrace, waiting, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)
  - Going down steps, OCT 15, 1959 (Box slides, Folder 32)